serverbeach.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy | ServerBeach

This Privacy Policy describes the manner in which SERVERBEACH LTD. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this web site

##  The Information We Collect

SERVERBEACH gathers customer information to improve the content on our Website, to enhance your online experience, and for other business purposes. SERVERBEACH takes reasonable measures to guard your information. We use reasonable technical solutions to make your visit to our Website as safe as it can reasonably be, but you should understand that no information system can ever be made 100% secure. SERVERBEACH may collect various types of personal information voluntarily provided by Users, including name, company name, address, telephone number, credit card number or other billing information, e-mail address, and other information such as survey responses. SERVERBEACH may also collect information about how Users use our web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the web site or the domains from which Users originate. We may use "cookies" to track how Users use our web site. A cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer and delivered through your Web browser. Most, if not all, commercial websites now use cookies. By using this technology, we can provide you with an enhanced online experience. It is possible for you to turn off cookies in your Web browser. If you do this, you can still browse our Website, but we will not be able to provide you with a more personalized experience.

##  How We Use Information

SERVERBEACH may use information collected through our web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by SERVERBEACH and its affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users' experience with SERVERBEACH and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. SERVERBEACH may also use information collected through our web site for research regarding the effectiveness of the web site and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of SERVERBEACH, its affiliates, independent contractors and business partners.

##  Disclosure of Information

SERVERBEACH may disclose information collected from Users to affiliates, independent contractors and business partners who will use the information for the purposes outlined above. We may also disclose aggregated data based on information collected from Users to investors in SERVERBEACH and potential partners. We may transfer information collected from Users in connection with a sale of SERVERBEACH's business. We may also disclose, in our sole discretion, any and all of your information including assigned IP numbers, account history, account use, etc. to any law enforcement agent who makes a written request, or in response to any request made in the civil discovery process, without further consent or notification to you.

##  Questions

Users may direct questions concerning this Privacy Policy by email to [privacy@peer1.com.](mailto:privacy@peer1.com)

SERVERBEACH may modify this privacy policy at any time without prior notice to SERVERBEACH's Customers or the public. Persons wishing to remain appraised of SERVERBEACH's privacy policy should check this page for occasional updates.

Users may elect not to receive solicitations from SERVERBEACH or from trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners by completing the opt-out request form [here](http://go.peer1.com/ServerBeachEmailUnsubscribe.html).

This Privacy Policy is effective as of February 10, 2009.
